<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>some thoughts on Einmal ist keinmal</title>
    <link>https://doNotBeTooSerious.github.io/tags/some-thoughts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in some thoughts on Einmal ist keinmal</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 04 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://doNotBeTooSerious.github.io/tags/some-thoughts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>我要拿你的头盖骨当碗使！</title>
      <link>https://doNotBeTooSerious.github.io/post/theyoung/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://doNotBeTooSerious.github.io/post/theyoung/</guid>
      <description>我要拿你的头盖骨当碗使！ 如果你要交易，请不要和我说情义。 如果你要服从，请不要欺我以忠孝。
不道德的东西往往需要拿道德辩护。 伤害人性的事情常常要拿利害服人。
如果真的没有选择，我们是否至少能有勇气把坏事办得像一件坏事？ 如同魔苟斯那样，也不失为一种诚实自信。
宁可把头盖骨输给维京人当碗使， 也不要将前列腺割给希腊人做太监。</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Camélia</title>
      <link>https://doNotBeTooSerious.github.io/post/cam%C3%A9lia/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://doNotBeTooSerious.github.io/post/cam%C3%A9lia/</guid>
      <description>Camélia 一条是痛苦，一条是爱情。这两条路走起来都十分艰难。那些女人在上面走得两脚流血，两手破裂；但与此同时，她们把罪孽的盛装留在沿途的荆棘上，赤条条地抵达旅途的尽头，而这样全身赤裸地来到天主跟前，是用不着脸红的。</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>cowardice and sins</title>
      <link>https://doNotBeTooSerious.github.io/post/cowardicesins/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://doNotBeTooSerious.github.io/post/cowardicesins/</guid>
      <description>Cowardice &amp;amp; Sins | 懦弱与邪恶 There was a time in chinese history when Lianzuo (which generally means to behead or punish other people who is in some way related to the person who is committed to a certain crime). Reportedly, it was invented by * Yingzheng *, the first emperor who united China. It was originally invented to ensure every peasant in his kingdom and army would unquestionly loyal to him and kingdom and all the peasants will force each other to obey the emperor out of fear for being punished by his / her companion&amp;rsquo;s fault.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>rehearsal</title>
      <link>https://doNotBeTooSerious.github.io/post/rehearsal/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://doNotBeTooSerious.github.io/post/rehearsal/</guid>
      <description>Rehearsal of Life Einmal ist keinmal, says Tomas to himself. What happens but once, says the German adage, might as well not have happened at all. If we have only one life to live, we might as well not have lived at all.
However, the long long history of our imperial past, told us to live in a scenario once and once more won&amp;rsquo;t bring us any further either. When everyone on this land forgets about Robespierre, he will certainly return, sometimes even with cheers of joy, he again, cuts off tens of thousand heads on this land, sometimes even with joy, like a show that forever is at rehearsal with then silent audiences.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>